http://www.webceo.com/privacy.htm#cookies

Yum, cookies! This site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to assist with navigation and support, and this also helps with our promotional efforts. Please accept cookies to make our site work properly. Cookie policy
Accept cookies
Menu
1-866-793-2236
online
Sign In
Sign Up
Pricing
Tools
Last Revision: June 22, 2020
WebCEO LP (hereinafter "WebCEO") is firmly committed to the privacy of its customers. WebCEO shall take all reasonable measures to have your personal information protected to ensure you feel safe and secure.
This Privacy Policy covers how WebCEO uses personal information that users provide to WebCEO when they use the WebCEO software service (hereinafter "WebCEO") through our software (cloud-based SEO platform) and our website located at https://www.webceo.com (the “Website”). Such service, the software and the Website are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “Service”. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. By using any of the services you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy.
How We Collect and Use Your Information
You can browse the WebCEO website, located at https://www.webceo.com, without providing any personally identifying information.
To start using WebCEO, you will need to register at
https://online.webceo.com
and provide some personal information such as a unique email address and password, or get authorized with your Facebook, Google, LinkedIn or Yahoo account. We may use your Personal Information to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, to help improve the Service, to customize your experience or to send updates or notices about the Service.
If you choose to link your Facebook, LinkedIn, Yahoo or Google account to WebCEO, you will be prompted to allow us to get access to your email and name from your Facebook, LinkedIn, Yahoo or Google account, and you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use what they send us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can delete your WebCEO account and thus the connection to your social media account or service account at any time by contacting our support team.
The information that WebCEO collects about you can be classified as Personally Identifying Information and Anonymous Information. Personally Identifying Information refers to information that identifies you as a person, for example, your name, postal address, phone number, email address, payment details. Anonymous Information refers to information that does not identify a specific individual. We may use and analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our website and the products and services we offer. We may collect information from third party service providers only upon your grant of respective permissions.
Personally Identifying Information (PII)
We collect your email address when you register in the Service. If you subscribe to one of the paid service plans in the WebCEO cloud-based SEO platform, we collect such information as your full name, billing address, credit card information, phone number and other billing information.
We may use your PII to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, to help improve the Service, to customize your experience at the Website, or to send updates or notices about the Service. We also use your PII to bill you for the Service subscriptions and other charges. The billing is performed by a third-party billing service that meets Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards securing your sensitive financial and billing information.
Anonymous Information
Every time you visit the Website, WebCEO collects certain technical information from your Web browser. This includes your internet connection, browser language, operating system, hardware specs, the pages that were visited and returned to, the time spent on the Website by a visitor, the referring site and any keywords used to find the Website on search engines. This information does not contain any reference to personal information. This information can only be accessed by
and can be used with the sole purpose of tracking visits to the Website and improve the experience, content and layout of the Website. Using the anonymous information, WebCEO can also identify defects in the Service and thus continually improve the quality of the Service.
Data Policy and Cookie Policy
As is common practice with almost all professional websites and services, this site uses cookies. Cookies are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer to improve your experience. This chapter describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the site’s functionality.For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies .
Cookies are also the cornerstone for any Web analytics solution that tracks interaction between a browser and a website. WebCEO uses information collected from cookies to track the pages of the Websites that our users view, the browsers they use and other information about user activity when visiting the Websites.
We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. We utilize Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, to better understand your use of our Website and Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Websites, what pages they visit and what other sites they used prior to visiting. Google uses the data collected to track and examine the use of the Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the Website to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. WebCEO has implemented Remarketing with Google Analytics for Display Advertising online. WebCEO and third-party vendors, including Google Inc., use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on a person's past visits to the Website. As a result, WebCEO's ads are displayed on sites across the Web. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Google offers an opt-out mechanism for the web available here.
We provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom's use of cookies, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.
If you are subscribed to the Service and you wish to log in to your Service account, your Web browser must accept cookies. A cookie/session variable is assigned to you when you log in, and is placed on your computer for programming purposes only. It ensures that you have properly logged in and that your personal information is only accessible to you. The Web browser's settings can be customized to refuse cookies and to remove them from your computer.
Connecting to Google Applications via the WebCEO service
WebCEO provides several tools that allow users to connect with certain Google services, such as Google Analytics, Google Search Console and Google My Business. WebCEO's Google Ads tool pulls data from Google Analytics so your Google Ads and Google Analytics accounts should be connected. Different WebCEO tools may ask for different permissions, so it is important to review the requested permissions before allowing access.
In order for these WebCEO applications to work properly, a user must begin the process by clicking the 'Connect' button. The user will be taken to a secure page on Google.com via a pop-up window or tab, where the permissions the tool requires will be displayed. If the user consents to grant WebCEO permission, Google will issue a token that our tools can use to access the requested information.
After receiving permission, WebCEO can, within the scope of the approved access, request information about, or data from, any profile the user has access to. For these tools, WebCEO uses a short-lived access token to request user Google Analytics, Search Console or Google My Business data.
The information that we request is used by our tools in calculations and visualizations about your selected data. We store the requested data up to 30 days to build reports and provide additional analytics data in various WebCEO tools. At the end of the specified period we delete the data and make a new request. If a user revokes access to the Google Analytics, Search Console or Google My Business data, we delete all previously requested data.
By default, our tools are able to see the email address of the user’s account. Our tools do not ever see or store a user’s password, as that is entered on a secure pop-up window or tab on Google’s website and not visible to us. At any time the user can revoke access to their Google Analytics, Search Console or Google My Business data in the WebCEO settings.
We shall not disclose, sell or rent your Google Analytics, Search Console or Google My Business data to any third party. We shall share your Google Analytics, Search Console or Google My Business data with the third parties only if you instruct us to and only if such information is required to provide you with specific services.
To monitor which tools by WebCEO and others tools, have been granted access to your information, and to see which permissions have been granted, review your connected applications here: myaccount.google.com/permissions
How We Use Cookies
Our website, like many others, stores and retrieves information on your browser using cookies and uses cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately, in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave all cookies alone if you are not sure whether you need them or not, as they may be critical to provide a service that you use.
Cookie provider
Cookie Name
Purpose
Storage time
Necessary
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website.The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
webceo.com
csrftoken
Helps prevent Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attacks.
1 year
online.webceo.com
sessionid
Used for proper work of our service
1 month
.webceo.com
_redirect_flag
Used for proper work of our service
3 months
Strictly recommended:
These cookies are recommended not to opt out of as this would cause incorrect operation of our web site functions.
Intercom.com
_mkra_ctxt
Used by our web site’s live chat
Session
Intercom.com
_mkra_ctxt
Used by our web site’s live chat
Session
persistent
Statistics:
Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Crazy Egg
_ceg.s
Used by the service Crazy Egg to track visitor sessions
3 months
Crazy Egg
_seg.u
Used by the service Crazy Egg to track visitors on our site
3 months
To refuse Crazy Egg cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
Google Analytics
_ga
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 years
Google Analytics
_gat
Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate
Session
Google Analytics
_gid
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website
Session
To refuse Google Analytics cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
Marketing:
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
google.com
ads/ga-audiences
Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor's online behaviour across websites.
Session
google.com
ads/user-lists/#
Used for Google ads
Session
google-analytics.com
collect
Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behavior. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.
Session
To refuse Google Analytics cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
facebook.com
fr
Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.
3 months
To refuse Facebook cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
doubleclick.net
IDE
Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user
2 years
doubleclick.net
test_cookie
Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies
Session
To refuse DoubleClick cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
twitter.com
personalization_id
Used by Twitter to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertiser
2 years
rubiconproject.com
put_#
Registers anonymized user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimizing ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network
Source: https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/conversion.js
30 days
To refuse Google Remarketing cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
facebook.com
tr
Used for Facebook conversion tracking
Session
To refuse Facebook cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies?"
Alternatively, please click on the relevant opt-out link
t.co
i/adsct
Used by Twitter to deliver a series of advertisement products
Session
quora.com
m-b
Events tracking by Quora
210 months
How Can I Control Cookies?
You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie preferences by clicking on the appropriate opt-out links provided in the cookie table above.To control cookies, you can modify your settings in most web browsers to accept or deny cookies or to request your permission each time a site attempts to set a cookie. Although cookies are not required for some parts of our services, the WebCEO site and service may not work properly if you disable cookies entirely. For example, you cannot log in if you've disabled all cookie use. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information. In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com .
How We Share Your Information
Privacy for our users is very important for WebCEO. We shall not disclose, sell or rent your Personal Information to any third party for marketing purposes. We shall share your Personal Information with third parties only if you instruct us to, and only if such information is required to provide you with specific services. We may share your Personal Information, but not credit card data, with a relevant Regional Exclusive Distributor for your area, who has signed a Nondisclosure Agreement, so your data is absolutely safe with us. We shall use an industry standard credit card processing company to bill our users for subscriptions and other fees. These third parties shall not retain, share or store any Personal Information except to provide these services and shall be bound by strict confidentiality agreements, which limit their use of such information.
WebCEO may disclose Personal Information to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by WebCEO, whether or not a response is required by applicable law. WebCEO reserves the right to transfer Personal Information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of WebCEO or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.We may use and disclose to third parties information we collect in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form for research and informational purposes and to help us make sales, marketing and business decisions.
How We Protect Your Information
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. WebCEO shall use all and every commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguard to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot warrant the security of any information you provide in the Service and you do so at your own risk. Once we have received any information from you, WebCEO shall make all and every commercially reasonable effort to ensure the security of our systems. Please note that this is not a guarantee that unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure and other factors that may at any time compromise the security of user information, will not happen.
Where you use a password for access to our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.If you are registered as a user, we also enable you to view the data about you yourself and, if applicable, to delete or amend it. If incorrect information is stored despite our efforts to ensure that data is accurate and up to date, we will correct it at your request.
Email Communications
WebCEO is committed to keeping your email address confidential. We shall never sell, rent or lease our user email lists or otherwise disclose the user email addresses to any third party. We shall use our users' email addresses exclusively to communicate WebCEO information to them. We respect your attention and time so we shall limit the frequency of our mailings to a reasonable amount.
WebCEO administrative and service announcements
WebCEO shall automatically email administrative messages such as "Thank you" messages or welcome messages introducing users to the Web CEO products and services, responses to password recovery, password and email change requests and similar explanatory messages that are necessary for user guidance. Users cannot opt-out from these emails.
WebCEO may email you service announcements such as day and time of expected interruptions of services, change of prices or service specifications. These emails have no opt-out status either.
WebCEO marketing communications
WebCEO may email marketing messages such as product updates and special offers. However these messages shall be sent only to WebCEO users and never to any third parties. Upon receipt of a WebCEO special offer or product update email message, users can opt out by clicking the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message.
Children Under the Age of 13
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes in Our Privacy Policy
Your use of the Services, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy,
WebCEO Terms of Service. WebCEO reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and such modifications shall be effective upon posting them on the Website. You agree to be bound by any changes to this Privacy Policy when you use the Services after any such modification is posted. It is, therefore, important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated of any changes.
Contacting WebCEO
If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please contact us at support@webceo.com.
CCPA Compliance Statement
Scheduled for January 1, 2020, CCPA regulates personal information collection and data usage by businesses. WebCEO LP complies with all laws and regulations applicable to its provision of the online services, which would include the CCPA.
California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the types of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to support@webceo.com.
GDPR Compliance Statement
On 25 May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the existing 1995 EU Data Protection Directive (European Directive 95/46/EC). WebCEO LP is committed to GDPR compliance. We have evaluated the new requirements and restrictions imposed by the GDPR and reviewed where and how we collect, use, store and dispose of personal data.
When processing data, we aim to ensure the following:
The processing is lawful, fair and transparent
The data is collected for a specific purpose and is necessary for the purpose
The data must be accurate and kept up to date
Data is not kept for longer than necessary
The data is kept safe and secure
We may collect the following PII: email address, full name, billing address, credit card details, other billing details, phone number.
Our servers are located in the EU and in the USA.
We do care about the security of your data. WebCEO allows you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. All our third party service providers are GDPR compliant to ensure that your data are protected. We have taken appropriate technical steps to ensure that we use the necessary level of protection for your information:
Data encryption in transit (HTTPS, IPSec, TLS, PPTP, SSH)
Data encryption in our database
Logging of actions and log analysis
Password policy for access to the production database
Changing of internal passwords
Access control (physical and technical)
Limited access to the production database at the network level
Firewall
Antivirus
DDoS protection
PCI DSS compliance
You can call us at +0-800-404-8180 (UK toll-free) or +1-866-793-2236 (US toll-free). Our company’s registration address is 39/5 Granton Crescent, Edinburgh, EH51BN, United Kingdom. Or email us with any questions to support@webceo.com.
Request an Agency Trial
Add more info to speed up your request
Request an agency trial
Thanks forsending your request!
If you want your site to be used during the interactive demo
Create a FREE WebCEO account
ALREADY REGISTERED?
Log in to your account during the demo.
You have previously submitted a B2B demo request. We will contact you shortly.
Request a B2B Demo
Add more info to speed up your request
Request a Demo
Thanks forsending your request!
If you want your site to be used during the interactive demo
Create a FREE WebCEO account
ALREADY REGISTERED?
Log in to your account during the demo.
You have previously submitted a B2B demo request. We will contact you shortly.
Quick Start Guide (pdf)
0-800-404-8180 (Europe Customers, Toll-free)
07:00 AM - 07:00 PM (GMT)
Monday through Friday
39/5 Granton Crescent, Edinburgh, EH51BN, United Kingdom
Back to Top
© 2001 - 2020 WebCEO LP. All rights reserved.
